http://www.longbeach.gov/privacy/

False Alarms
More »
Planning Permits
More »
Towing & Lien Sales
More »
Planning & Building Forms
More »
Tobacco Permits
More »
Green Business
More »
Calendar/Agendas & Minutes
Who Do I Call?
Towing & Lien Sales
More »
Code Enforcement
More »
Rancho Los Cerritos
More »
Business Associations
Belmont Shore
4th St. (Retro Row)
Bixby Knolls
East Anaheim (Zaferia)
Magnolia Industrial Group
Uptown
More »
Travel Resources
Convention Visitors Bureau
GIS Maps & Data
Long Beach Airport (LGB)
Long Beach Transit
Parking Services
More »
Library
Long Beach Airport (LGB)
Privacy
Home »
Privacy
City of Long Beach Website Privacy Statement
Introduction
The City of Long Beach recognizes that technology has changed the nature and accessibility of government business information and the prospective use of that information. While committed to applying technology to improve access to information, we are strongly committed to protecting your online privacy. The purpose of this statement is to inform you about the types of information we gather when you visit our web site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, the security precautions we take to protect your privacy, and how to contact us if you have questions or concerns.
Collection of Information
We collect information that is used for analysis and statistical purposes that help us manage the City of Long Beach’s web site. Also, we collect information to assist us in delivering service and information to you. (1) Information collected for statistical purposes We automatically collect electronically generated information about your visit to our site, such as the date, type of browser used, and technical Internet protocol data. We collect this information about each user session from our use logs, and refer to it for statistical purposes. (2) Information provided when using our interactive forms and functions This information may include such things as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and other personal and business data, depending on that particular service you use. We collect only those data necessary to provide the service that you are requesting.
Use of Information
If you send us an e-mail message with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, or fill out a form that transmits this information, we will only use the personally identifiable information to respond to your request and analyze trends. We may redirect your message to another government agency or person in a better position to answer your question. In order to provide you with the ability to receive directed e-mail information in which you have expressed an interest, it is necessary for the City of Long Beach to collect your e-mail address. This information is used only for e-mail distribution to the specific list or lists for which you have registered. By agreeing to use this service, you are granting us permission to send you periodic e-mails only about topics for which you registered. The City of Long Beach will use your e-mail address only for this permission based e-mail service.
Disclosure to Third Parties
As a government agency, the City of Long Beach is governed by public records laws. Any information that we receive through use of our web site is subject to the same provisions as information provided on paper. Otherwise, we do not share personal identifying information with any third party without your permission. We disclose only in aggregate form our statistical analyses or users’ demographics to third parties. This information is not reported or released to any outside parties unless we are legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings. Further, we do not reveal any e-mail address information to third parties for independent use unless you specifically authorize us to do so.
Sale of Data
The City of Long Beach does not sell data for direct mail or advertising purposes.
Security
The City of Long Beach’s web servers contain state-of-the-art industry security precautions that prevent personal information from being stolen or tampered with. If you submit a credit-card number, that information will be protected by secure server software (SSL), which encrypts all information before being securely sent across the Internet. Also, we limit employee access to personally identifiable information to only those employees who need access to perform a specific job. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.
Control of Personal Information
At any time while accessing our web site, any user while online may decline participation in any activity that asks for information ( e.g., survey, e-mail, e-commerce). Your choice not to participate will in no way affect your ability to use any other feature on our site. We also offer you the permanent option to unsubscribe from any and all e-mail lists maintained for our listserv service. Users may at any time choose to remove themselves from any list.
Children
No application on the City of Long Beach’s web site specifically solicits information from minors or seeks to determine whether the visitor is a minor. Consequently, visitors should be aware that the collection of personal information requested from or volunteered by children online or by e-mail will be treated in the same manner as information given by an adult. This information may become a public record, and as such may be subject to public access. We ask that parents guide their children when children are asked to provide personal information online.
Translation
The City of Long Beach has added a translation feature powered by Google Translate to assist citizens in understanding information on this website in a variety of foreign languages. Please be aware that Google Translate, a free third party service which the City does not control, provides automated computer translations that may not give you an exact translation all the time.
Disclaimer
This site provides links to other sites. This privacy policy applies only to the City of Long Beach’s web site. When you link to any other web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that site. Visitors linking to another site are encouraged to examine the privacy statement of that site. While the City of Long Beach attempts to maintain current data throughout its website, we regret that this may not always be possible. Neither the City of Long Beach, nor any agency, officer, nor employee of the City of Long Beach warrants the accuracy, completeness, reliability, or timeliness of any information published on this system, nor endorses or recommends any content, viewpoint, products, resources, or services linked from this system and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, completeness, reliability, or timeliness of such information. Portions of such information may be incorrect, or not current. Any person or entity that relies on any information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk.
Contact
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, or about the web site in general, you may e-mail the City of Long Beach web manager at webmaster@longbeach.gov
Do.
Pay Utility Bills
Get Licenses and Permits
Recycle. Reduce. Reuse.
Meetings Live
Discover.
Information Near You
DataLB
City Calendar
Meetings & Agendas
Connect.
Social Media
Mobile Apps
LinkLB
Speak Up LB
Ask.
Who Do I Call
Your City Officials
Privacy Policy
Social Media TC
